Dorothy Kenyon Papers, 1850-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
"Wiretapping in New York Today," remarks for radio broadcast 4/60 Box 22
"Wiretapping," speech delivered at Cooperative Institute 7/60 Box 22
"Wiretapping 7/60 Box 22
"Wiretapping Must Go," speech delivered to NYU Forum Discussion at the Arthur Garfield Hayes Memorial 5/61 Box 22
"Civil Liberties 10/62 Box 22
"Constitutional Law 175 Years Later," speech delivered to Phi Beta Kappa at College of William and Mary 12/62 Box 22
"Wanted: Action Not Words 12/62 Box 22
"The Role of the Supreme Court 12/62 Box 22
"Growth with the Times," speech delivered on unidentified occasion in Seattle, WA 4/66 Box 23
"Sex Crimes and Civil Liberties," speech delivered to Kalamazoo and Detroit Civil Liberties Unions 4/68 Box 23
Civil rights and racism
Untitled remarks ["I am shocked to hear that the American Bar Association has rejected"] for The People's Choice 4/43 Box 20
Material for speech made before Interfaith Movement meeting 3/44 Box 20
Untitled excerpts ["It's Un-American What do we mean by that?"] from speech at Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League 5/44 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech ["The interfaith movement is organized for tolerance in all things"] for the Interfaith Movement 12/44 Box 20
Untitled speech "Refugees from Hitler--international bill of rights...."] 1945 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Last time at Williamsburg, Phi Beta Kappa... ."] about discrimination and segregation delivered at 1949 National Conference of the American Alumni Council 1949 Box 21
"States' Laws on Race and Color," article for unidentified publication 5/51 Box 21
"The McCarran Act," speech delivered to East Side ADA and American Jewish Council meeting on McCarran Act 3/55 Box 22
"International Aspects of Civil Rights," speech delivered to Phi Beta Kappa chapter at Dartmouth College 4/55 Box 22
"McCarran Act Meeting," remarks delivered by DK as presiding officer 6/55 Box 22
Untitled speech about racism and American history ["Promise of American life--a tragic topic"] delivered to Rabbi Wise Free Synagogue Women's Group 3/56 Box 22
"ADA's Integration Project," speech delivered at ADA Meeting on Integration 5/57 Box 22
"Arabs and Israelies," speech delivered to Phi Beta Kappa chapter at University of Vermont 12/57 Box 22
"ADA Congratulates Board of Education on Harlem School Decision," statement issued by DK on behalf of ADA 2/59 Box 22
"Advancing the Frontiers of Freedom," research and speech delivered to Committee to Honor Vern Bullough in Youngstown, OH 6/59 Box 22
Untitled speech about civil rights ["Voting blocked--in South by intimidation, unfair registration..."] delivered to Croton Westchester branch of Americans for Democratic Action 2/60 Box 22
Untitled speech about Civil Rights bill ["We are here today in behalf of civil rights and to assess our responsibilities"] delivered to ADA Conference on Civil Rights 2/60 Box 22
Untitled speech about civil rights ["Registration provision--applications may file statements with president"] delivered to YWCA Public Affairs Committee 3/60 Box 22
"Civil Rights Today," speech delivered at Elmira College 5/60 Box 22
"Questions on Race, Ethnic Group and Religion on Census Schedules and Registration Forms," speech delivered to American Sociological Association 4/61 Box 22
Untitled remarks on housing and civil rights delivered at 22nd National YWCA Convention 5/61 Box 22
Untitled speech about civil rights delivered at Westchester ADA meeting 5/63 Box 23
Untitled speech about civil rights delivered as Phi Beta Kappa speech at University of Connecticut and College of William and Mary 5/63 Box 23
"Habits Frozen," speech delivered to Women's Division of Episcopal Diocese of Newark NJ 10/63 Box 23
"Civil Rights," delivered to panel on civil rights at Skidmore College 3/64 Box 23
Untitled remarks introducing James Farmer at LCDC (?) meeting 6/65 Box 23
"Jane Crow and Lily-White Males," printed article in Civil Liberties n. 233 1/66 Box 23
"Frontiers of Civil Liberties," speech delivered to Annual meeting of Kansas Civil Liberties Association 4/67 Box 23
Untitled tribute to A. Philip Randolph delivered at party honoring him 1/70 Box 23
Untitled remarks for panel discussion on The Politics of Fear n.d. Box 23
Consumer and cooperative issues
"The Supreme Court speaks" 1929 Box 18
"Memorandum Presented by Representative of the Consuming Public in Opposition to Certain Proposals for Local Rules of Fair Trade Practice for the Hotel Industry" 4/34 Box 18
Untitled speech delivered to Consumers' League 1/35 Box 18
"The Customer is Always Right..." speech for League of Women Shoppers 9/35 Box 18
"Food" remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 12/35 Box 18
"Minimum Wage," remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 4/36 Box 19
"Guinea Pigs, Consumers and Cooperation," remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 5/36 Box 19
Untitled remarks before Consumers' Cooperative Society(?) 1/36 Box 19
"Death and Taxes," remarks at Annual Meeting of Consumers' Cooperative Society 3/36 Box 19
"Unions," remarks at CCS meeting 10/7/36 Box 19
Untitled remarks on CCS strike 1/2/37 Box 19
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast on cooperatives 12/37 Box 19
Untitled remarks "Country of pioneers--individualists"] delivered on unidentified occasion 3/8/38 Box 19
"Cooperative Lectures" delivered on unidentified occasion 3/38 Box 19
"Individualistic Country," remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 8/38 Box 19
"Milk, Women, Babies" 4/37 Box 19
"Electric Light," remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 12/37 Box 19
"High Cost of Living" remarks delivered on unidentified occasion 1/38 Box 19
"Cost of Living," notes for remarks at Bronx ALP 2/38 Box 19
"Milk," notes for Rand School Lecture 9/38 Box 19
"Maintaining Standard of Living," remarks for Cooperative Conference 3/39 Box 19
Untitled notes for lecture re 3/39 Box 19
Untitled notes for remarks delivered to Annual meeting of Wholesale 5/39 Box 19
"Fields Not Yet Open to Women," outline and speech delivered before conference of Institute of Women's Professional Relations 11/39 Box 19
Untitled notes for remarks at Rand School 2/40 Box 19
Untitled remarks ["which kind do we want?"] about incorporation of cooperatives in Amherst, MA 8/41 Box 20
Untitled article for The Cooperative Crier about government during wartime 1942 Box 20
"Cooperatives 9/43 Box 20
"Cooperative Principles," speech at Parkchester Houses 12/43 Box 20
Untitled radio script ["How did you first become aware of..."] for program celebrating Consumer Cooperative Centennial 9/44 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech ["We are Young"] at Albany Cooperative Society 12/44 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech at Cooperative Society in Caldwell, NJ 10/44 Box 20
Untitled speech about wages and prices for Council of Jewish Women in Yonkers 1/44 Box 20
Untitled speech about housing shortage for conference in Amherst, MA 8/46 Box 20
"Europe Revisited," speech for Consumers Cooperative Society 9/46 Box 20
"Taxation of Cooperatives," remarks for debate at Bronx Men's Club 11/46 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech ["Dreams--what to talk about"] for Gramercy Branch of Consumer Cooperative Society 2/47 Box 20
"Cooperative Housing," remarks delivered at Cooperative Institute at Haverford College 7/48 Box 21
"Non-Cooperation in the Near East," remarks delivered at Cooperative League 5/18/49 Box 21
"Cooperatives in World Trade," speech delivered at University of Michigan Law School Summer Institute 8/49 Box 21
"The Functions of Management, Board and Members in a Cooperative" 9/53 Box 21
"Problems of Expansion," speech delivered at Consumer Cooperative Society annual meeting 6/54 Box 22
Notes for untitled speech ["Rochdale--depression period"] delivered at J_____ Cooperative Society in Philadelphia 12/55 Box 22
Untitled remarks about health insurance plans delivered at symposium on health insurance plans 4/57 Box 22
"Middle Income Housing - America's #1 Housing Need," speech delivered to Cooperative Association circa late 1950s Box 21
"Cooperation, Self-help and Economic Democracy," speech delivered to Morningside Heights Consumer Cooperative 3/61 Box 22
"Ten Year Change," speech delivered to Cooperative Institute 7/61 Box 22
"Cooperators and Consumers" 6/67 Box 23
Education
"The Presidency of Mount Holyoke College 10/36 Box 19
"Educating Our Youth," remarks for radio broadcast 12/38 Box 19
"Evening Schools," notes for remarks at Committee to Save Our Night Schools 1/40 Box 19
Untitled notes ["Education, as usual, is out for the duration"] for speech 3/43 Box 20
Untitled notes for speech ["My deficiencies--Committee, not college prof. or even president..."] for Phi Beta Kappa Council 9/46 Box 20
Untitled speech ["I am happy to be tonight in a city of brotherly love"] delivered at Founder's Dinner, Women's Medical College of Pennsylvania 3/50 Box 21
"A Layman Looks at the Liberal Arts," speech delivered at Founders Day Convocation, Dickinson College 5/50 Box 21
"Education for Women Spring 1951 Box 21
"Educated Women and Controversial Issues" 2/51 Box 21
"The Spirit of the Times," speech delivered at Hunter College Phi Beta Kappa celebration of 175th Anniversary 12/51 Box 21
"The Responsibility of Scholars in the World Today," speech delivered at Phi Beta Kappa Society of Marietta College 4/53 Box 21
"Crisis in Our Schools," speech delivered to Queens American Jewish Congress 2/56 Box 22
"Women and Outer Space," speech about coeducation delivered at Wheaton College 3/58 Box 22
"Women and Outer Space," speech delivered at Dickinson College 3/58 Box 22
"Education as a Human Right," speech delivered to UPA at PS 96 2/59 Box 22
"Civil Liberties in Education," speech delivered to Phi Beta Kappa initiates at Kalamazoo College 5/59 Box 22
"School Bond Issue 10/59 Box 22
"The Adventure of Scholarship," speech delivered to Phi Beta Kappa Association of Long Island 12/59 Box 22
Outline for article on liberal education n.d. Box 23
Untitled fragment of remarks about labor education for women ["But just as the movement for women's education is young, so also it is growing"] delivered at Smith Club meeting n.d. Box 23
Labor issues
The Manufacturers' Child Labor Program 11/27 Box 18
Socialist Elections 10/31 Box 18
Homework 1/35 Box 18
How the Courts Handle Labor Cases 12/35 Box 18
Thursday Speech 1935 Box 18
Minimum Wage 4/36 Box 19
Security--Minimum Wage 5/36 Box 19
"Why Minimum Wage?" notes 10/36 Box 19
"Unions 10/7/36 Box 19
Untitled remarks ["Went to see Meistersinger"] for American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 7/37 7/37 Box 19
Statement at Albany Minimum Wage Hearing, 2/37 2/37 Box 19
"Organization Among Government Employees" 2/37 Box 19
DK's introduction of Mary Simkhovitch, chair of NYC Municipal Housing Authority, 2/37 2/37 Box 19
Memorandum in Opposition to Moffat-Nunan Bill 5/37 Box 19
"Rickets and Rackets 10/38 Box 19
Untitled notes for speech at Brooklyn Labor Party 1/38 Box 19
Untitled notes for speech on Staten Island 2/38 Box 19
Untitled speech before nurses group 8/38 Box 19
Untitled remarks for SCMWA meeting at Carnegie Hall 10/38 Box 19
Untitled remarks to Labor Club 11/38 Box 19
Untitled notes re 2/39 Box 19
"Labor in a Democracy," notes and speech for American Labor Party 3/40 Box 19
"Women's Participation," notes for remarks to American Labor Party 3/40 Box 19
Untitled remarks to ALP 8/40 Box 19
Untitled speech ["War does strange things..."] at Labor Standards Conference 2/44 Box 20
"Carlo Tresca," notes for speech delivered at Tresca Memorial Committee meeting 1/49 Box 21
Untitled speech about Irving Brown delivered at League for Mutual Aid Annual Dinner 3/63 Box 23
Untitled fragment of remarks about labor education for women ["But just as the movement for women's education is young, so also it is growing"] delivered at Smith Club meeting n.d. Box 23
League of Nations
Untitled ["There is no one perhaps more astonished than I..."] 3/38 Box 19
"Women Enter a New World," article for The Woman's Press 6/38 Box 19
"Geneva Looks at Women's Status from Independent Woman" 6/38 Box 19
"The League of Nations and the Legal Status of Women 7/38 Box 19
"The Threat to Women in the New European Alignment and What Geneva is Doing to Help," remarks to New York Business and Professional Women 11/38 Box 19
The Law and the legal profession
A Woman Lawyer Looks at Her Profession 5/35 Box 18
Women and Government 4/36 Box 19
"Government Bureaus and the Lawyer 9/38 Box 19
"Can Girls Be Lawyers," in The American Girl 3/39 Box 19
"My First Case on the Bench," remarks to American Labor Party 3/39 Box 19
"The Poor Man's Court" 10/39 Box 19
Untitled notes on NYC court system 11/39 Box 19
Untitled remarks ["Justice is the odd man..."] for West Side Synagogue 12/40 Box 19
Untitled remarks ["Plaintiff nurse employed by defendant municipal corporation..."] for St. Johns Law School 4/41 Box 20
Untitled speech ["Birth of the law..."] for Smith College 11/41 Box 20
"Criminal Field," notes for speech 11/41 Box 20
"Judges and the Law" 12/41 Box 20
"The School, the Family and the Courts," speech for Missouri State Teachers Association 1941 Box 20
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast about crime and criminals 12/49 Box 21
"Death and Taxes," notes for discussion about legal matters 2/52 Box 21
"A Lawyer's Life," speech delivered to Student Honors Convocation at Miami University of Ohio 4/54 Box 22
"Juvenile Delinquency," speech delivered to Long Island branch of ADA 6/55 Box 22
"Career Vistas," speech delivered to Iota Tau Tau Sorority and NYU Law School 4/56 Box 22
"Court Reforms," remarks delivered to NY ADA 3/58 Box 22
"Lawyer and Judge," article in unidentified YWCA publication 5/59 Box 22
"Life as a Judge and Lawyer," speech delivered to NY chapter of Alpha Omricon Pi 10/59 Box 22
"Lawyers and Ethics," speech delivered to Westchester Ethical Culture Society 12/68 Box 23
Outline for discussion of lawyers' role in a democracy--defense of the unpopular n.d. Box 23
"Remarks of Judge Dorothy Kenyon n.d. Box 23
"Socialization of the Law" n.d. Box 23
"Law and Foreign Relations" n.d. Box 23
Political campaigns
Republican Platform 1925 Box 18
Speech for Al Smith 11/28 Box 18
Socialist Election 10/31 Box 18
Speech for Harry Schneiderman, 1/35 1/35 Box 18
Untitled speeches about American Labor Party 10/36 Box 19
Woman Lawyer for Consumers' Services Backs Roosevelt 10/36 Box 19
Remarks for American Labor Party about Quack Medicine Bill and Child Labor, 1/38 1/38 Box 19
Untitled remarks for American Labor Party meeting 6/38 Box 19
Untitled congratulatory remarks to women of American Labor Party 11/38 Box 19
"Judicial Campaign Issues," remarks for radio broadcast 10/39 Box 19
Notes for campaign speeches, DK's judicial campaign 11/39 Box 19
"The Walter Logan Bill," radio broadcast 4/40 Box 19
Untitled remarks for Women's Council of "The Fund" 5/40 Box 19
Untitled speech about Wendell Wilkie's sexism 10/40 Box 19
Untitled speech about Wilkie campaign 10/40 Box 19
"Why I Shall Vote for Alfange," speech to American Labor Party 10/42 Box 20
Untitled speech for Roosevelt at Saturday's Children 11/44 Box 20
Untitled remarks about NYC political candidates ["This is a vital city election in more ways than one..."] for "Women of the Hour" broadcast: typescript 10/49 Box 21
Notes for untitled speech for unidentified candidate ["I have heard that in a war a general is only as good as his chief advisors..."] n.d. Box 23
"Bob Wagner," radio speech for candidacy of Wagner 10/53 Box 21
"No Endorsement for Attorney General," speech at Americans for Democratic Action State convention 9/54 Box 22
"2 1\2 Minutes," speech for unidentified political candidates 2/55 Box 22
Untitled radio broadcast speech for Adlai Stevenson delivered at Fordham University 5/56 Box 22
Untitled list of questions asked by DK as moderator of Democratic Presidential Candidates radio debate 6/56 Box 22
"Badge of Courage," speech for Robert Wagner at ADA State Convention 9/56 Box 22
"Our Next President," speech delivered to Volunteers for Stevenson, Paramus, NJ 1956 Box 22
"Kenyon for Kefauver 10/56 Box 22
"Nixon's Policies," speech opposing Nixon given at unidentified occasion 10/56 Box 22
Notes for untitled remarks delivered at Democratic Women's Division Campaign Rally for Mayor Wagner 10/57 Box 22
"Speech for Harriman," delivered at ADA State Convention 9/58 Box 22
"Al Wilman as a Liberal," speech delivered to New Chelsea Democratic Club 5/59 Box 22
"School Bond Issue 10/59 Box 22
"Speech for Bob Trentlyton," delivered to New Chelsea Club 1/60 Box 22
Untitled speech for Barbara Whitmore delivered to New Chelsea Club 3/59 Box 22
"Hubert Humphrey for President," speech delivered at Lenox Hill Club 3/60 Box 22
Untitled speech for Mayor Wagner delivered to New Chelsea Club 7/61 Box 22
"Running for Executive Council," speech for DK by DK delivered to New Chelsea Club 1/62 Box 22
Untitled speech for Judge Harold Burns delivered at meeting of Reform Democratic Club 7/65 Box 23
Untitled speech ["Political freedom is a matter of individual conscience..."] delivered to ADA 10/65 Box 23
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast in favor of candidate Ted Weiss 9/66 Box 23
Untitled campaign speech for Fiorello LaGuardia ["as citizens of a democracy that functions well only at the price of eternal vigilance..."] n.d. Box 23
Untitled notes for speech about Labor Party n.d. Box 23
Politics and political activism
Changing the Constitution 4/26 Box 18
Know Your Own Government 7/32 Box 18
Our Social Courts 7/35 Box 18
Working for the City 3/36 Box 19
Using Political Machinery for Social Ends 3/36 Box 19
Social Legislation--License Business in the Public Interest 4/36 Box 19
What We Have 4/36 Box 19
Technique of Utilizing American Political Machinery to Secure Social Action 5/36 Box 19
Untitled speech about how women can change the world, 11/36 11/36 Box 19
"The Responsibility of the Lawyer in the City," speech for Phi Beta Kappa 12/36 Box 19
Untitled speech at Horace Mann School 12/36 Box 19
"Behind the Scenes at the License Department" 1936 Box 19
"Some Immediate Responsibilities of University Women in Molding Public Opinion" 1936 Box 19
Difficulties in the Way of Amendment 7/37 Box 19
"Running a City," for Smith Alumnae Quarterly 2/37 Box 19
"Running a City," for Municipal Reference Library Notes 4/37 Box 19
Notes for radio broadcast, [Running a city is a big job] 1937 Box 19
"Suggested paragraphs to be inserted in speech by Miss Dorothy Kenyon at Come-and-See Luncheon," 10/37 Box 19
"Declaration of Independence" 1937 Box 19
Untitled notes ["California System..."] 9/30 Box 18
"Reform Legislation," speech for Buffalo Phi Beta Kappa 12/40 Box 19
Untitled speech ["The impulse to live is one of the strangest..."] for the Greater New York Fund 2/41 Box 20
Untitled notes for remarks in Jane Clark's Government class at Barnard College 5/41 Box 20
Untitled remarks ["We get used to things so fast..."] about city government, Bronx, NY 10/41 Box 20
Untitled notes ["my speech in Brooklyn..."] for speech at Jewish Council 2/43 Box 20
"Do Americans Have Different Laws in Different States?" radio broadcast of "United States of American 'Answering South Africa'" 12/43 Box 20
"A Citizen in Government," discussion course sponsored by League of Women Voters and chaired by DK 2/45 Box 20
Untitled remarks ["I remember the first time I ever voted"] for radio broadcast about importance of voting 11/47 Box 20
Untitled remarks about liberalizing the Republican Party for ABC Broadcast of "On Trial" 12/48 Box 21
"Stand Up for Freedom 6/50 Box 21
Untitled speech ["Far cry from League of Nations to Chelsea..."] about importance of "selling" democracy 10/50 Box 21
"A Strong Democracy--How Women Can Build It," speech delivered to Nassau County Woman's Forum 4/52 Box 21
Untitled speech about treaty amending proposals ["Should Association support amendment?"] delivered at County Lawyer's Symposium 10/52 Box 21
"The National Scene--Time for a Change is Here," speech delivered to Americans for Democratic Action-North Shore Branch 1/53 Box 21
Untitled remarks ["Welcome ADAers..."] delivered at Americans for Democratic Action City Wide Meeting 12/53 Box 21
Untitled remarks ["Mr. President Truman and friends of ADA"] delivered at New York ADA Roosevelt Day Dinner 2/54 Box 22
"As ADA Sees the Current Scene," speech delivered to West Side ADA Branch 4/54 Box 22
"No Endorsement for Attorney General," speech delivered at ADA State Convention 9/54 Box 22
"Congressional Issues," speech delivered to Christian Action 10/54 Box 22
"The Issues," speech delivered to Greenwich Village branch of ADA 1/55 Box 22
"American Role in Today's World," introductory remarks delivered at New York ADA 4/55 Box 22
Untitled speech delivered at ADA City Convention in NYC 10/55 Box 22
Untitled speech ["Last time I came you turned an alarm clock on me..."] delivered to Village Branch of ADA 1/56 Box 22
"Plight of the Intellectual," speech delivered to Phi Beta Kappa Association of Milwaukee-Downer College 2/56 Box 22
"Challenge of Intellectualism," speech delivered at Ohio Wesleyan 4/56 Box 22
"The Scholar's Responsibility for Truth and Courage," speech delivered at Queens College 5/58 Box 22
"The Role of the ADA," speech delivered at West Essex County ADA 8/58 Box 22
Untitled speech ["Speak on behalf of the somewhat turgid prose of the senate resolution..."] about individual rights and freedoms delivered to Phi Beta Kappa Annual Meeting 8/58 Box 22
"The Supreme Court--Its Place in Our Government," speech delivered to YWCA 10/58 Box 22
"The Supreme Court?" speech delivered to New York Smith Club 3/59 Box 22
"The Supreme Court 1/60 Box 22
"The Role of the Supreme Court 3/59 Box 22
"Court Reform," speech delivered to Nyack branch of AAUW 4/59 Box 22
"The Role of the Supreme Court 5/60 Box 22
"Off-Track Betting," article in ADA State News 5/60 Box 22
"How to Get Good Judges," speech for radio broadcast 8/60 Box 22
"Towards Better Judges," report of a Special Committee of the Citizens Union by DK, Nathaniel Singer, David Korn 1960 Box 22
"Moore Commission Charter," speech delivered to New Chelsea Club 2/61 Box 22
Untitled speech about political reform ["Chelsea club is two years old..."] delivered to New Chelsea Club 6/61 Box 22
"A Unique Institution--The Great American Gamble," speech delivered at Brooklyn Institute 6/62 Box 22
"Patronage Abuses Workshop," speech delivered to meeting of NYCDV on Patronage Abuses 1/62 Box 22
Untitled speech on Supreme Court delivered to Phi Beta Kappa at Lafayette College 4/62 Box 22
Untitled speech on structural position of Executive Committee under club charter delivered to New Chelsea Club 7/62 Box 22
"Human Rights and Its Champion 7/62 Box 22
"Judicial Reform and Patronage," speech delivered to NYU Students for Democratic Reform 4/63 Box 23
Untitled remarks for radio broadcast on NY politics ["Practical point of view..."] 6/66 Box 23
"Towards Better Judges," speech delivered at NYU Law School 10/68 Box 23
Untitled speech delivered at meeting of Chelsea Citizens Against the Stolport 7/70 Box 23
"Landmarks Preservation," remarks delivered to the Landmarks Preservation Society 1970 Box 23
Untitled remarks delivered to N.T.E.A. (?) n.d. Box 23
"Constitution--Unamendable?" notes for speech delivered on unidentified occasion n.d. Box 23
"Place in the Constitution," notes for speech delivered on unidentified occasion n.d. Box 23
"Changing the Constitution n.d. Box 23
"Municipal Housekeeping n.d. Box 23
"Problems of Local Government," notes for speech delivered on unidentified occasion n.d. Box 23
Poverty
Untitled speech delivered to Mayor Lindsay's Task Force on Poverty 2/66 Box 23
"Anti-Poverty Elections," speech delivered at UJD(?) Club 5/66 Box 23
Untitled speech on law offices for the poor, delivered at community meeting at DK's house 6/66 Box 23
"Neighborhood Law Offices for the Poor," speech delivered to League for Mutual Aid 6/67 Box 23